德雷克
Oh Drake.
抱歉  安柏
I'm sorry Amber.
布莱德就是这样子  总得争个赢
It's just like Brad to have to have the last word.
抱歉  我迟到了  怎么样
I'm sorry I'm late, what happened?
我们在看结局
We, we just wanna see the end.
我要你  德雷克
I want you Drake.
这个我知道  但我们永远不可能有结果的
I know you do but you and I can never be together that way.
什么
What?
有件事我一直没有告诉你
There's something I never told you Amber.
其实我是你的异母哥哥
I'm actually your half-brother.
那后来怎么样呢
So what happens next?
我为连体婴做分割手术  得了医学奖
Well, I get the medical award for separating the siamese twins.
然后我跟安柏去委内瑞拉
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela
找另外一个异母哥哥雷蒙
to meet our other half-brother, Ramone.
我在那里找到了全世界最大的翡翠
And that's where I find the world's biggest emerald.
真的很大  但受了诅咒
It's really big but it's cursed.
天啊  真是个好剧
God that is good TV.
菲比  跟我玩嘛
Come on, Pheebs, play with meeee.
不  这种游戏太荒谬了
No. This game is grotesque.
把二十个无臂男人
Twenty armless guys
用钢棒穿过腰间串成一串
joined at the waist by a steel bar,
被迫无止境地踢足球
forced to play soccer forever.
简直是侵犯人权嘛
Ahh, hello, human-rights violation.
菲比  不要为他们难过
Ya know Pheebs, don't feel so bad for'em.
等他们踢完足球后
After they're done playing,
我会把小塑胶妞拿出来
I break out the little plastic women
大家都非常开心呀
and everybody has a pretty good time.
你干嘛不跟你室友玩
Why don't you play with your roommate?
他不爱玩桌上足球
Ah he's a, he's not a big fan of foosball.
你跟那个新来的处得不好吗
Uh oh, ooh, are we not getting along with the new boy?
不是啊  他很好
No he's, he's alright,
只是多数时间他都关在房里
just uh, he spends most of his time in his room.
那也许是因为  你没花时间去了解他
Maybe that's because you haven't taken the time to get to know him.
我们来补救  好不好
Let's remedy that, shall we?
我们不需要补救
We don't need to remedy that.
要啊  会很好玩的
Oh yeah, it'll be fun.
什么事
What was that?
你好  我只是想我们三个
Hi, um, I just thought that it would be fun
来点啤酒  彼此了解一下会很有意思
if the three of us had some beers and got to know each other.
好的  听起来不错
Yeah alright, that sounds alright.
太好了
Oh good, ok.
不行  我得走了  因为我还要赶去参加
Oh nooo, I have to go because I'm late for my um,
"绿蛋与火腿"研讨会
Green Eggs and Ham discussion group.
今晚的主题是
Um tonight it's
"为什么他不在火车上吃呢"
why he would not eat them on a train.
好好玩  拜
Have fun bye.
好烂的借口
That was so lame.
我知道  你跟他谈谈吧
I know, yeah. Ok, talk to him.
你觉得那个极速赛车手会被开很多罚单吗
So, you uh, you think that Speed Racer guy gets a lot of tickets er?
好笑  好笑  那是谁甩了谁啊
That's good, that's good. So, so, so who broke up with who?
开什么玩笑  我甩了她呀
What're you kidding? I broke up with her.
她真的以为肖恩·潘是柬埔寨的首都
She actually thought that Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.
太好笑了  大家都知道
That's good man, when everybody knows that the uh,
柬埔寨的首都是
the capital of Cambodia is uh...
-不是肖恩·潘  -不是肖恩·潘
- Well it's not Sean Penn. - Not Sean Penn.
好吧  我也有个好笑的
Alright, I, I've got a funny one, alright.
我前女友提莉  我们在吃早餐
My last girlfriend Tilly. Ok, we're eating breakfast, right,
我做了很多煎饼  大概有五十个吧
and I made all these pancakes, there was like 50 pancakes right.
突然间她转过来  她说"艾迪"
And all of the sudden she turns to me, alright, and she says, 'Eddie.'
我说"什么事"  她说"我不想再看到你了"
I say, 'yeah,' she says, 'Eddie, I don't want to see you anymore.'
那就好像是  她把手伸进我的胸膛里
And it was literally like she had reached into my chest,
挖出了我的心
ripped out my heart,
将心上的鲜血涂抹在我的生活中
and smeared it all over my life, ya know.
现在我面前就像有一个万丈深渊
And now there's like this incredible abyss, ya know,
我就一直往下掉  往下掉
and I'm falling and I keep falling
永无止境地往下掉
and I don't think I'm ever gonna stop.
这个故事不太好笑  是不是
That uh, wasn't such a funny story, was it?
一个坏脾气老头说我尽量
And a crusty old man said I'll do what I can
其他老鼠开始摇沙锤
and the rest of the rats played moroccas.
唱完了  谢谢  晚安
That's it, thanks, good night.
菲比有别的工作吧
Phoebe's got another job, right?
唱得很好  菲比
Great set tonight Pheebs.
我知道
I know.
我想我们该走了
Well, we should probably get going.
我们也该走了  明早八点还有病人
Um, we should go too, I got patients at 8 in the moring.
知道吗  我在想
Ya know, I was thinking.
我们老是在你那边过夜
Ya know how we always stay at your apartment?
或许今晚改住我这边吧
Well, I thought maybe tonight we'd stay at my place.
不知道  我没有带睡衣
I don't know, I don't have my jammies.
或许你不需要
Well, maybe you don't need them.
我的小妹妹  各位先生女士
My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.
闭嘴  我很快乐
Shut up, I'm happy.
这太棒了  我必须要说几句
Oh, this is so nice. Alright I have to make a speech.
我只是想说  在莫妮卡交往过的
I just wanna say that of all the guys that Monica has been with,
为数众多的男友中
and that is a lot,
我最喜欢你了
I like you the best.
谢谢你  菲比  你嘴真甜
Oh, thank you Pheebs. That's very sweet.
听到了吗  她最喜欢我
Hear that? She likes me best,
而且你显然阅人无数
and apparently there've been a lot.
没有啦  菲比在说笑  她是疯子
Not a lot, Phoebe's kidding, Phoebe's crazy.
菲比死定了
Phoebe's dead.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我找艾迪·曼诺威克
I'm looking for Eddie Minowick.
他现在不在  我叫钱德勒
Oh, uh, he's not here right now, uh, I'm Chandler,
要我帮你传话  还是拿鱼缸呢
can I take a message, or, or a fishtank?
谢了
Thanks.
请进
Oh, oh, c'mon in.
我叫提莉
I'm Tilly.
看你这个样子  他一定跟你提过我了
I gather by that oh that he told you about me.
提过  你的大名在一段
Oh yeah, your uh, name came up in a uh,
令我惊心动魄的对话中  曾经出现过
conversation that terrified me to my very soul.
他这人有点激烈吧
He's kind of intense huh?
对呀  请问你艾迪是不是有一点...
Yes. Hey, can I ask you, is Eddie a little...
有一点怎么样
A little what?
有点乡村
Bit country?
快进来呀  室友
C'mon in here you roomie.
你好  提莉
Hello Tilly.
艾迪  我只是把鱼缸送过来
Eddie, I just came by to drop off your tank.
你想得真是周到  非常周到
That's very thoughtful of you. It's very thougtful.
就这样了  我走了  拜
Well, ok then. I'm gonna go. Bye.
再见
Bye-bye.
Bye.
我们要养鱼吗
So, we gettin' a fish?
你们上床了  是不是
You had sex with her didn't you?
菲比  你看  你看...
Pheebs, check it out, check it out, check it out, check it out.
《肥皂剧文摘》  我最喜欢的文摘之一
Oh, ooh, Soap Opera Digest, oh that's one of my favorite digests.
42页...
Page 42, page 42, page 42.
好的  好的  医界新秀
Ok, ok, ok. Ooh, hey 'new doc on the block,
《我们的日子》乔伊·崔比安尼
Days of Our Lives' Joey Tribbiani.'
好帅的照片
Ooh, cool picture.
我好帅
Ooh, I look good.
这是真的吗  很多台词都是你自己写的
Hey is this true, that you write a lot of your own lines?
可以这么说啦
Uh, well, kinda yeah.
记得上周  亚历克斯出事那一集吗
Like, remember last week when Alex was in the accident?
剧本上的台词是
Well the line in the script was,
我们不送这女人去医院的话  她会死的
'If we don't get this woman to a hospital, she's going to die.'
被我改成了  这个女人不去医院的话
But I made it, ' If this woman doesn't get to a hospital,
她就活不成了
she's not gonna live.'
我懂你做了什么了
Ohh, ok, I see what you did there.
那你不怕
Aren't you afraid though,
那些编剧看到这篇文章会生气吗
that the writers are gonna be kinda mad when they read this?
是嘛  我倒没有考虑过那些编剧
Huh? Never really thought about the writers.
剧本总是送来我家
The scripts just kinda come to my house.
但你知道吗  这样让我很有面子
But you know what? This makes me look good,
就让电视剧有了面子
which makes the show look good,
也让编剧有了面子
which makes the writers look good
他们怎么可能会生我的气呢
so how could they be mad about that?
他写了自己大部分的台词  混蛋
Makes up most of his lines. Son-of-a-.
很好  看我怎么收拾你
Yeah, well, write this jerkweed.
我跌下了电梯井
I fall down an elevator shaft?
这什么意思  我跌下了电梯井
What the hell does this mean, I fall down an elevator shaft?
我不知道  我只是送剧本过来
Uhh, I don't know, I just bring the scripts.
他们不能杀我
They can't kill me,
我是弗朗西斯卡失散的儿子呀
I'm Francesca's long lost son.
对  请你签收好吗
Right. Could you sign this?
不可能  我才不签呢
No. No way, I'm not signing that.
我不认为这对剧情会有什么影响
I don't think that's gonna affect the plot of the show.
他们怎么能这么对我
How can they do this to me?
我要走了  很遗憾
Er, uh, I'm just gonna go. Sorry.
也没有那么多个啦
Well it wasn't that many guys.
如果你考虑到全世界有多少男人的话
I mean, if you consider how many guys there actually are,
那个比例是非常小的
it's a very small percentage.
没什么大不了的  我只是好奇罢了
Hey, it's not that big a deal, I was just curious.
晚安
G'night.
晚安  理查德  好运  莫妮卡
Night Richard. Good luck Mon.
好吧  我说之前
Alright, before I tell you, uh,
你先说你有过几个女人
why don't you tell me how many women you've been with.
两个
Two.
两个  才两个  那怎么可能
Two? Two? How is that possible?
你知道你长得有多帅吗
I mean, have you seen you?
我能说什么呢
Well, I mean what can I say?
我跟芭芭拉做了三十年的夫妻
I, I was married to Barbara for 30 years.
我们在高中就认识了
She was my high school sweetheart,
加上你  一共两个
now you, that's two.
那就两个吧  该睡觉了  我去刷牙了
Two it is. Ok, time for bed, I'm gonna go brush my teeth.
你先等一等  来啊  换你了
Woah, woah, no wait a minute now. C'mon it's your turn.
快说呀
Oh c'mon.
我不需要确切的数字
Ya know, I don't need the actual number,
大概就行(也指棒球场)
just a ballpark.
反正肯定比一个棒球场的人数要少
Ok, it is definitely less than a ballpark.
真庆幸现在我不是莫妮卡
Wow, I am so glad I'm not Monica right now.
那还用说  你的神奇数字是多少
Tell me about it. So what, what's your magic number?
说嘛  我交往过的你都认识  就两个
C'mon, you know everyone I've been with. All, both of them.
有你
Well, there's you.
最好不要说我是第一个
Better not be doin' these in order.
比利·崔斯津  彼得·卡尼
Ok, uh, Billy Dreskin, Pete Carney,
巴瑞  还有
Barry, and uh, oh,
保罗
Paolo.
对  意大利来的蠢驴
Oh yes, the weenie from Torrini.
亲爱的  你嫉妒保罗吗
Oh honey, are you jealous of Paolo?
我跟他在一起  从没像
Oh, c'mon, I'm so much happier
-跟你在一起这么快乐过  -真的
- with you than I ever was with him. - Really?
拜托  跟保罗那一段连交往都算不上
Oh please. That Paolo thing was barely a relationship.
那只能算是无意义的野兽般的性关系
All it really was was just, ya know, meaningless animal sex.
这话在我脑中听起来不是这个味道
Ok, ya know, that sounded soooo much better in my head.
艾迪  我没有跟你的前女友上床
Eddie, I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.
有意思
That's very interesting, ya know,
因为跟她上过床的人  都会这么说
'cause that's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.
你疯了  你疯了
This is nuts. This is crazy.
她只来了两分钟而已
She came over for like two minutes,
放下鱼缸就走了  就是这样
dropped off a fish tank, and left, end of story.
巴迪在哪里
Where's Buddy?
巴迪
Buddy?
我的鱼巴迪
My fish, Buddy.
她只带了鱼缸  缸里没鱼
There was no fish when she dropped it off.
这真令人难以置信
Oh, this is, this is unbelievable.
你先跟我的前任女友上床
I mean, first you sleep with my ex-girlfriend
以为我会笨到去相信你的谎言
then you insult my inteligenct by lying about it
然后你杀了我的鱼  我的巴迪
and then you kill my fish, my Buddy?
我没有杀你的鱼啊  你听我说  艾迪
Hey I didn't kill your fish. Look Eddie...
瞧我在做什么呀
Would you look at what I'm doin' here.
这样太不明智了
That can't be smart.
所以我们把这家伙从你身上拿开
So we're just gonna take this guy right off ya
把它放到我的口袋先生里
and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
来个橘柚吧
Tangellon?
就这样吗  这就是
That's it? That's the
你害怕告诉我的庞大数目吗
giant number you were afraid to tell me?
是啊
Well yeah.
那还好嘛
Well, that's not bad at all.
你害我以为有一个舰队那么多
I mean, you had me thinkin it was like a fleet.
你真的觉得没关系吗
You really ok with it?
亲爱的  没关系
Oh honey, I'm fine.
太好了
Oh, yay.
关于那两个
Ok about that two.
什么  好吧  我的"两个"怎么了
What? Alright, what about my two?
只是听起来真的好少哦
Well, it just seems like a really small number.
对  还有呢
Right, and...
还有  难道你不想到处拈花惹草吗
And, well, don't you have a lot of wild oats to sew?
或者你现在就是这个态度
Or is that what you're doing with me?
天啊  我是路边的野花吗
Oh my God, am I an oat?
亲爱的  你不是被采的花
Honey, you are not an oat.
我不知道  我想我不是喜欢拈花惹草的人
I, I mean I don't know, I, I guess I'm just not an oat guy.
我只跟我爱的女人上床
I've only slept with women I've been in love with.
但是你只跟两个人上过床
But you've only slept with two people.
对
Right.
你知道我也爱你吧
You know I love you too, right.
现在我知道了
Now I do.
罗斯  拜托听我说
Ross, Ross, please listen to me.
罗斯  你比保罗好太多了
Ross, you are so much better for me than Paolo ever was.
你关心我  你有爱心  你逗我笑
I mean you care about me, you're loving, you make me laugh.
如果我逗你笑  我有个主意
Oh, hey, if I make you laugh, here's an idea,
不如你邀请保罗过来在床上野兽一下
why don't you invite Paulo over and have a little romp in the sack
而我就站在角落讲敲门的笑话
and I'll just stand in the corner and tell knock-knock jokes.
老天  罗斯  我们的感情很特别
God, Ross, look, what you and I have is special,
我跟保罗有的只是
all Paolo and I ever had was...
野兽般的性关系
Animal sex, animal sex?
所以你什么意思呢  你是说
So what're you saying, I mean, you're saying that like,
我们之间就没有任何"兽性"的东西吗
there's nothing between us animal at all.
甚至连小小的"兽性"都没有吗
I mean there's not even like, uhm, a little animal,
甚至连  连"花栗鼠性"都没有吗
not even, not even like, like chipmunk sex?
罗斯  拜托你听我说
Ok, Ross, try to hear me.
我不想对你说谎  跟保罗的性爱是很好
Ok, I, hey, I'm not gonna lie to you. Ok, it was good with Paolo.
敲敲门
Knock-knock.
但是
But,
我们两个所拥有的比那好多了
what you and I have is so much better.
我们有温柔  我们有亲密
Ok, we have tenderness, we have intimacy,
我们灵犀相通
we connect.
我发誓
Ya know, I swear,
这是我拥有过的最棒的
this is the best I have ever had.
直到现在
Until now.
理查德刚说他爱我
Hi. Richard just told me he loves me.
天啊  亲爱的  太棒了
Oh my God, honey that's great.
我知道  只是我找不到...
I know. I just can't find...
在第一个抽屉  快
Oh they're in the top drawer. Hurry.
你也要啊
You need one too?
对呀
Ooooh yeah.
找到了
Found it.
只有一个
There's only one.
莫妮卡
Monica.
我马上来  我们在决定事情
Hi. Uh, we'll be right there, we're just trying to decide something.
瑞秋
Rachel.
她们两个在决定事情
They're just trying to decide somehting.
好  很好
Good, good, good.
你的小胡子  跟以前有不同吗
So, is uh, was your moustache, did, used to be different?
没有
No.
你怎么能够保持得那么整齐
How do you uh, ya know, keep it so neat?
我有一把小梳子
I have a little comb.
那个梳子叫什么
And what do you call that?
胡子梳
A moustache comb.
我帮你洗一个月的衣服
Ok, I, I will do your laundry for one month.
不
No.
好吧  我会  我会
Ok, ok, ok, I will, I will,
我打扫两个月的房子
I, hey, I will clean the apartment for two months.
好的  这样吧  只要你告诉我
Alright, I tell you what, I'll give this to you now
簸箕放在哪里  这个现在就给你
if you can tell me where we keep the dustpan.
你有没有打过越战
So were you in Nam?
剪刀石头布
Rock-paper-scissors?
没问题
Yeah.
一二三
One two three.
太棒了
Yeesss.
很好  上床吧
Fine, go have sex.
不对  你完完全全搞错了
No. You have got it completely wrong.
约翰·萨维奇演的是《猎鹿人》  没有腿
John Savage was Deerhunter, no legs,
约翰·沃伊特演的是《归乡》  腿瘫痪了
John Voit was Coming Home, couldn't feel his legs.
不对  你完完全全搞反了  朋友
No, no way. You've got it totally the other way around my friend.
约翰·沃伊特是...
John Voit was...
亲爱的
Honey.
什么
What, what oh....
进去吧
Shall we?
今晚不可能了  今天晚上他们做
It's not gonna happen. They're doing it tonight,
我们可以明天再做
we can do it tomorrow.
以后  可不可以先让我看看时间表
Uh, in the future, if I could see the schedule beforehand...
我今天早上醒来的时候
So, when I woke up this morning,
发现他偷了我所有的鞋垫
he'd stolen all the insoles out of my shoes.
为什么
Why?
那家伙以为我睡了他前女友  还杀了他的鱼
Because he thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
你干嘛杀了他的鱼
Why would you kill his fish?
菲比  因为有时候你跟人上床之后
Because sometimes, Phoebe after you sleep with someone,
就必须要杀条鱼
you have to kill the fish.
钱德勒  亲爱的  真抱歉
Chandler honey, I'm sorry.
可以看乔伊的电视剧了吗
Ok, can we watch Joey's show now please?
等等  他还没有到
Wait, he's not here yet.
他是其中角色  他知道情节
So, he's on the show, he knows what happens.
对了  我不在乎我的问题了
Oh, I'm fine about my problem now, by the way.
很好
Oh good.
安柏  我想你知道
Amber, I want you to know that
我会永远支持你的
I'll always be there for you,
我是你一辈子的朋友跟兄弟
as a friend and as your brother.
德雷克
Oh Drake.
辛苦了  先是医学大奖  然后是这个
Hard day huh? First the medical award, this.
是呀  我想有些人就是天生好运
Yeah, some guys are just lucky I guess.
拉莫瑞医生  请立即到一楼急诊室报到
Dr. Remore, report to first floor emergency, stat.
那么  看来在叫我了
Well then, uh, I uhh, guess that's me.
还有谁想坐电梯的
Anyone else need to go on the elevator?
霍顿医生  翁医生
Dr. Horton, Dr. Wong?
他们只叫你一个人啊
No, no, they only said you.
好吧  我去吧
Oh, ok. Alright.
我爱你  德雷克
I love you Drake.
好  随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
不好
Oh no.
德雷克  小心
Drake, look out.
他们刚刚杀了乔伊吗
Did they just kill off Joey?
不
No.
现在好像是的
Now maybe.
-快开门  -乔伊
- Come on. - Joey.
开门  我们想跟你谈一谈
Open up. We want to talk to you.
我不想谈
I don't feel like talkin.
别这样了  乔伊  我们关心你
Oh c'mon Joey, we care about you.
我们很担心你
We're worried about you.
有些人真的很尿急呀
And some of us really have to pee.
抱歉  乔伊
Sorry Joey.
听着  很遗憾你的死  真的很惨
Listen, sorry about your death, that really sucks.
我们一看到就赶过来了
We came over as soon as we saw.
你怎么不告诉我们呢
How could you not tell us?
我不知道  我有点希望没有人会发现
I don't know, I was kinda hopin' no one would ever find out.
或许他们可以让你起死回生
Well, maybe they can find a way to bring you back.
不会  他们说找到我尸体时
Naa, they said that when they found my body,
我的脑袋已经摔得稀巴烂了
my brain was so smashed in that
而唯一救得了我的人是我
the only doctor that could have saved me was me.
说是故意要看起来讽刺什么的
Supposed to be some kind of irony or somethin.
乔伊  你不会有事的
But Joey, you're gonna be fine.
你不需要那个节目  那只是个很蠢的肥皂剧
You don't need that show, it was just a dumb soap opera.
菲比  这是我这辈子最棒的事
Phoebe, this was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
没错  我本来是要那样说的
Yes, I was going to incorporate that.
很好  莫妮卡来了  她会说句好听的啦
Oh good, here's Monica, she'll have something nice to say.
我把你的浴帘拉开了  以免发霉
Um, I straightened out your shower curtain so you won't get mildew.
怎么了  我觉得这是好事啊
What? To me that's nice.
不要紧的  你知道的
It's gonna be ok. You know that.
不  我不知道
No, I don't.
就好像你奋斗了一辈子去追求
It's like, ya know, you work your whole life for somethin'
你会认为当你办到的时候
and you think that when you get it
永远不会像你想的那样好
it's never gonna be as good as you thought it would be.
不过这个就跟想象的一样好  它改变了一切
But this so was. Ya know, it changed everything.
那天  我收到一张信用卡申请表
Like the other day, I got this credit card application,
竟然是预先批准的
and I was pre-approved.
我这辈子从没被预先批准过
I've never been pre-approved for anything in my life.
很遗憾  老兄
I'm sorry man.
乔伊  我不知道这对你有没有意义
Yeah, Joey honey, I don't know if this'll mean anything to you
但我们永远会预先批准你的
but you'll always be pre-approved with us.
不  对我没有意义
No, that means nothin to me.
核桃饼  刚出炉的
Pecan sandy, just made em.
好的
Yeah alright.
这是什么  葡萄干吗
What're these, raisins?
当然了  有何不可
Uh, sure, why not.
听我说  艾迪
Listen Eddie, um,
我想过我们目前的合住情况
I've been thinking about our current living situation
你为什么要笑
and uh, why are you smiling?
我有个小小的惊喜  我新买了条鱼
I got a little surprise, look. There's a new fishie.
我叫它钱德勒  以你为名
I named him uh, Chandler, you know, after, after you.
这根本不是一条真鱼啊
Well that's not an, even a real fish.
这是金鱼饼干
No, that's a goldfish cracker.
你要说什么
What's you point man?
晚安了
Ok, good night.
你这个大变态
You big freak of nature.
今天晚上好冷
Ohh, brisk tonight.
可不是
Oh man.
以后永远别提这事
Let's never speak of this.
没问题
You got it.